KAROLINA ANKIEWICZ

Junior Full-Stack Developer | PHP, Laravel, Wordpress

CONTACT

- **▼** KAROCREATIVEDESIGNS@GMAIL.COM
- **(**048)-510304535
- in linkedin.com
- karocreative.pl
- github.com/g-i-kala
- GDYNIA PL

SUMMARY

I am a Full-Stack Web Developer with over 2 years of experience in creating, maintaining, and optimizing websites and web applications based on WordPress, WooCommerce, and Laravel.

Proficient in PHP 7/8 (OOP), MySQL, HTML5, CSS3, and JavaScript, I also have experience in delivering projects according to client requirements, with attention to code quality, RWD (Responsive Web Design), and UX design.

My skills include working with Git, Docker, and Composer, as well as performance and SEO optimization. Currently, I am focusing on the development of modern backend and full-stack applications using PHP, SQL, and JavaScript. I have basic knowledge of unit testing and process automation and I am eager to continue developing these skills to create even better applications.

EXPERIENCE

KaroCreative

Founder & WordPress Full-Stack Web Developer • 01/2022 - Present

- Creating and developing web applications and websites (PHP, Laravel, MySQL, WordPress, JavaScript, Tailwind CSS).
- · Maintaining and updating client systems according to provided documentation.
- Optimizing website performance, security, and SEO.
- Implementing and integrating APIs in e-commerce projects and web applications.
- Website migrations, server management, and configuration of PostgreSQL/MySQL databases.
- Developing custom plugins and themes and troubleshooting technical issues.
- Working according to best coding practices clear, maintainable code.
- Client collaboration, technical support, debugging, error analysis.
- · Work environment: Git, Docker, Composer.

Previous Career in Sound Engineering

Sound Engineer & Technical Lead • 01/2007 - 01/2020

- Managed teams and coordinated audio projects in fast-paced, dynamic environments, always meeting tight deadlines.
- Solved technical challenges and integrated advanced digital tools and automation systems.
- Collaborated closely with clients to deliver tailored audio and technical solutions.

EDUCATION

Master of Science (MSc) in Audio and Video Engineering

Gdańsk University of Technology • Gdańsk • 09/2003 - 06/2008

Certifications

JavaScript, PHP, SQL, React, TypeScript, UI/UX Design, Regular Expressions • 02/2023 - 06/2023 Codecademy

SELECTED PROJECTS

KaroCreative • 01/2022 - Present

Role: Full-Stack Web Developer (Founder)

- Designed and developed custom web platforms and stores using PHP, Laravel (basic to intermediate), WordPress & WooCommerce.
- Developed RESTful integrations with third-party services and built reusable components for e-commerce features.
- Actively improved codebases, optimized DB queries, and followed best coding practices.

GitHub Project Collection - q-i-kala

Role: Developer

- A collection of projects demonstrating skills in PHP development (OOP, MVC), Laravel, custom WordPress solutions (themes), API integration, and database management.
- Independent application development, refactoring, basic testing (PhpUnit/Pest).

SKILLS

Back-End & Database:

- PHP (OOP, MVC), Laravel in progress)
- MySQL, PostgreSQL, REST API
- Pest. PhpUnit basics
- WordPress custom features, WooCommerce,

Interests:

- Kitesurfing Coaching &Freestyle, Music Production,
- Reiki & Mindfullnes
- · Graphic Design

Front-End Development:

- HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQeury, React (foundations)
- Tailwind CSS, Bootstrap, Sass
- Responsive Web Design (RWD)
- WCAG & Accessibility

Workflow & Dev Tools:

- Git, GitHub, Docker, Composer, NPM, Jira, VSCode, Terminal
- · Figma, Affinity Designer

Soft Skills:

- Analytical thinking skills
- Independence and problemsolving ability
- Attention to detail and aesthetics
- Strong motivation for development and learning new technologies

LANGUAGES

• English: CEFR Level: C2 (Proficient).

• German: CEFR Level: B2-C1.

· Polish: Native.

Italian: CEFR Level: B1.

• Spanish: CEFR Level: A2-B1.